{
    "id": "aa848c0b0bea4be787dd10ba1678c2f1",
    "title": "A, An Or The",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "39a7ff3abfc34d628062ad2a2fe47828",
            "title": "A, An Or The",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "My son loves ………………………………",
                    "description": "We do not normally use the article the with plural and uncountable nouns when we are talking about people or things in general.",
                    "answers": [
                        "horses",
                        "a horses",
                        "the horses"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My sister is ……………………………..",
                    "description": "The article a/an is used for classifying people or things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "journalist",
                        "a journalist",
                        "the journalist"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please don’t use your nail as …………………………….. screwdriver.",
                    "description": "The article a/an is used for classifying people or things.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "No article"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can you recommend …………………………… good dentist?",
                    "description": "The article a/an is often used with a similar meaning to one.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "No article"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… must have patience.",
                    "description": "The article a/an can be used with the same meaning as any. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Teacher",
                        "A teacher",
                        "The teacher"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………… usually start talking at around 18 months old.",
                    "description": "No article is usually used with plural nouns when we are talking about people or things in general.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Children",
                        "The children",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you lock ………………………………door?",
                    "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which door is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "No article"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We hired ………………………………… to go to Mangalore.",
                    "description": "The article a is used here because the listener does not know which taxi is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "taxi",
                        "a taxi",
                        "the taxi"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did you do with ………………………………. vacuum cleaner I lent you?",
                    "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which vacuum cleaner is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "No article"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Did you enjoy ……………………………….?",
                    "description": "The article the is used here because the listener knows which party is meant.",
                    "answers": [
                        "party",
                        "a party",
                        "the party"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am ………………………………. youngest in my family.",
                    "description": "The article the is used before superlative adjectives. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "a",
                        "the",
                        "No article"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We went to ……………………………… school.",
                    "description": "We usually use the article the with same. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "same",
                        "the same",
                        "a same"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}